(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2=
(Today, the Earth Group bid farewell to)
(the elegance and romance of France.)
(Crossing mountains and seas,)
(they arrived in Chengdu,
the Land of Abundance.)
(From the adorable
black-and-white cuties)
(at the Chengdu Research Base
of Giant Panda Breeding)
(to the well-executed martial-art moves)
(of the Qingcheng Sect)
(and further on to the rich,
numbing-spicy Sichuan cuisine feast.)
(They explore)
(and savor along the way,)
(experiencing)
(the vibrant, down-to-earth
human warmth of this city.)
=Episode 9 (Part 2)=
(Kung Fu Panda)
Come in.
We got here first.
You go ahead.
Sorry.
Recording in the bedroom?
Sit down.
Lie down.
Take off your shoes.
(Get into bed right now)
Someone's coming.
(Lin Yi)
Hello.
Here.
Come on.
Get under the covers, hurry.
You took off your shoes already.
The first part is
to return to dreamland.
Really? We...
Are we starting like this?
Someone's coming soon.
Let's just pretend to be asleep.
Okay.
Coming.
It looks just like
the three of us slept here
last night.
Who is it?
Hello.
Here.
Where are you?
Bro.
What?
Where?
Sit down.
Come in.
What?
Come on, squeeze in.
Not bad.
Come on.
Honglei, your hair looks great today.
You...
What happened to your hair?
You're finally back.
He doesn't have neat bangs anymore.
Yes.
Why did you change your hairstyle?
I'm in an idol romance drama this time.
You look really stylish now.
Sit down, bro.
Close the door.
Whoever doesn't show up gets pranked.
So it must be Liu Yuning.
Guo Jingfei isn't here either.
Yes.
Yeah, Fei isn't here either.
He...
(Silently locks it)
He's not feeling well today.
What's wrong?
He's on crutches.
What?
He's got gout.
Really?
Oh, my.
(He really has gout)
Now, I'm...
They locked you out.
Won't let me in?
So handsome.
Right?
(Nothing but good looks)
So handsome.
I can...
I can hang out outside by myself.
What's going on out there?
Feels like a wedding chamber prank.
I think.
There is a bit of that vibe.
Block the door.
I locked it.
Don't let him in.
Ask for red envelopes.
(Follow the proper procedure)
Answer 10 questions correctly to get in.
Red envelopes.
(Still showing off)
While knocking on the door,
I even have to strike a pose.
(Not showing off on purpose,
just natural charm)
Who is it?
Sun Honglei.
Who's Sun Honglei?
My idol.
Guess who the bride in this room is.
What do you think?
You and me...
You got short hair too.
You've gotten thinner, bro.
They paired us up again.
Really? Just us two?
They won't let us in.
(Yuning, give it a try)
What's wrong with them?
Aren't they pranking us today?
No way.
(Time to fire up our brains)
Any prank needs someone to play along.
Just ignore them.
Don't forget. We're the big brains.
(Big brain is in action)
Yeah, leaving us out here.
Sit, bro.
(Not taking the pressure)
Wait for them to come find us.
Yeah.
They'll find us on their own.
Exactly.
(Perfect prediction)
Listen up, you guys outside!
How come they're ignoring us?
What are they doing?
How have you been lately?
Fine.
Time to go inside.
You're so good.
Right?
Looks good, right?
Very good.
(Drawn by the sound)
What happened to him? Let me see.
(So handsome
I have to lean against the wall)
Fei.
Have I lost a lot of weight?
So handsome.
Really?
You got me curious.
Everyone came out.
(Too rushed to even put on shoes)
Hello.
How come you're on crutches?
How are you doing?
Got gout.
Guo Jingshou.
Nice and lean.
[*Pronounced as "Jingshou" in Chinese]
Has our show come to this?
Just filming in one room?
(No filter at all, bro)
Is this the legendary
American quiff?
I don't know.
This is...
Because I cut my hair short.
Makeup artist...
Both of us have new hairstyles.
Can you stop looking in the mirror?
Please.
He keeps checking himself out.
You've got gout, fine.
Take your hands out.
(Hehe)
Stop striking poses over there.
I went light on makeup today.
(The best is yet to come)
I didn't even do eyeliner.
Next episode I'll put on false lashes.
I'm telling you.
He keeps checking himself in the mirror.
Look.
Look at Yuwen.
He keeps checking himself in the mirror.
Stop looking in the mirror.
You're blocking my view.
Let's get back on track.
Welcome, everyone,
to Chengdu, the Land of Abundance.
This land boasts rich resources
and an amazing variety
of mouth-watering food.
Whether you're here for great eats
or to soak up the laid-back vibe,
Chengdu makes
a fantastic travel destination.
This is where
we kick off the final stop
of our trip this season.
And a big welcome back
(Welcome home)
to Jun.
Thanks.
Happy wrap!
(Gong Jun)
But I heard
there is one more person coming back.
Are you reading off a script?
Yeah, you...
Just like that.
But I heard
there is one more person coming back.
Exactly that vibe.
No.
Like a little host.
So, next up...
So, who's next?
He's back too.
Good.
(He is getting sleepy from waiting)
(Chen He)
What on earth are they doing?
I've waited ages.
(Thinking about He)
Since he's been away for so long,
we've prepared
a little welcome ceremony.
(Chen He's exclusive welcome ceremony)
It's called "Good Morning, Princess."
Why "Princess"?
Because he's Princess Chen.
He's known around as "Princess".
Just like you're known as "Visual King".
(Visual King)
Same logic.
Oh.
(Putting on airs)
Simple and clear.
Got it.
Strikes a pose
right after being praised.
He is like this.
Like this.
(Visual King Imitation Show)
You...
You're only doing thirty percent
of his vibe.
He was just like...
(Visual King Imitation Show)
Yeah, old-money style.
Old-money style. Okay.
Fei.
Your foot doesn't hurt
when you're teasing others?
All better now.
Let's go play football later.
So, later,
you need to meet up with He,
and wake him up.
Within ten minutes,
help Chen He finish his styling,
take a group photo
and send it to AI.
Get the AI to judge that
Chen He is the most dazzling person
among the nine.
And without He noticing,
complete three sets of secret missions
one after another.
(Secret missions?)
No way.
I need to get a plan.
What's wrong?
Guo Jingfei...
(Block it)
I've had enough of him.
I'm really not looking in the mirror.
Seriously?
You just said one sentence,
but looked at the mirror six times.
What?
How come I got stuck with
this character?
This isn't me.
Let me read mine first.
Good Morning, Princess Secret Missions.
Mime Kung-Fu Ball Games.
Three out of the eight members
will be chosen
to hold the mime ball-sports games
in He's room.
Here are the events.
First, basketball.
Two members pass an imaginary ball
from the living room,
get the ball into He's area,
finish with an air jump shot,
and then slide in
for a knee-slide celebration.
Human bowling.
One member does mime bowling.
The rest split into three rows
and act out getting knocked over
and falling down.
This sounds absolutely ridiculous.
Even an idiot could tell
what we're doing.
I think there's only one way.
Shut his mouth.
Don't need to cover his mouth.
Just cover his eyes instead.
Let's just cover his eyes completely.
We'll wash his hair
and get shampoo suds
right into his eyes.
(So ruthless)
Wait.
You're so ruthless.
This boy has gone bad.
Already gone bad.
Successfully gone bad.
You have really gone bad.
Yeah.
Let's assign everyone's roles.
Okay.
Human bowling
is actually the hardest.
Well.
(Secret Mission: Mime Kung-Fu Ball Games)
We have to act as the bowling pins.
(1. Basketball 2. Human Bowling (Everyone))
Stand in a bowling-pin triangle.
Then one person does this.
We have to fall.
Trust me.
For the bowling part,
we just act it out.
He won't care about us.
He'll watch us play.
No. If he says,
"They're playing bowling",
then...
(If Chen He guesses the secret mission,
the challenge fails)
Logically,
we still need to keep him
from seeing what we're doing.
The fun just lies in
how we manage to get it done.
Fate is fair to everyone.
Yuning.
Now, you're the only big brain left.
(For now, only got looks)
I'm stepping out for now.
You're just eye-candy now.
I spent so long shaking off this label,
(I'm helpless too)
and now it's back.
Oh, my.
What you're saying
really hurts.
There is another event.
We need two members
for basketball.
We should pick two quirky people
for this.
Even if he notices,
he'll think it's reasonable.
We've got no shortage of quirky people
in this group.
But Lin Yi is the quirkiest one.
Right.
(The quirkiest of the quirky)
You pick one
as your teammate.
Then I'll go with him.
Him and me.
(Secret Mission:
Mime Kung-Fu Ball Games)
(1. Basketball: Lin Yi, Chen Xingxu;
2. Human Bowling: Everyone)
We'll go by eye contact.
Eye contact.
There's more.
Two more missions.
This is just a small part.
Three out of the eight members
change into
Bad Lei style outfits in the room,
reenact a classic quarrel scene,
and end up hugging and crying.
If the reenactment gets interrupted,
you need to start over.
Acting again?
This can't be done.
Let's watch the clip first.
(Clip from the TV drama, Full Bloom)
So everything now
- Lin Yi has to play this part.
- revolves around the kid.
Why are you arguing
right after getting back?
Do you still have dinner?
Well, Mom.
Just eat your food.
Mind your own business.
Can you speak Mandarin in front of me?
This is my son's house.
What's wrong with me speaking
my dialect with my son?
Do I get criticized even for
taking care of you every single day?
It's just a few lines in my dialect.
Is this really necessary?
What do you think my mom
is doing all this for?
Which dialect should we use?
(Perform it in dialect)
Just use our own dialect.
Two people need to
speak their native dialect.
Both of them have to
speak Sichuan dialect.
Really.
Who else can speak it?
Yuwen.
You speak Wuhan dialect.
(Start right now)
Yeah.
Forget it.
Nobody had it easy.
Don't do that.
Why are you arguing
right after getting back?
You give it a try.
Wait.
How about this?
I'll play the mother-in-law.
(Wang Yuwen as the male lead's mom)
Jun will play the husband.
Who plays...
(Gong Jun as the male lead)
Who plays the wife?
Beauty.
Honglei or Naiwen.
The beauty just needs to speak Mandarin.
(Take it naturally)
Can I speak Tianjin dialect?
Sure.
Already in character.
Just feel it.
(Li Naiwen plays the female lead)
I'll say it in Tianjin dialect.
So everything now
revolves around the kid?
Why are you arguing
right after getting back?
Do you still have dinner?
Well, Mom.
Just eat your food.
Mind your own business.
Wait.
Can you speak Mandarin in front of me?
(Surprisingly perfect fit)
These three people.
It's just the three of you.
Just you three. No doubt about it.
Good.
You still have to cry.
(Takes on the crying scene)
You need to cry.
Anyway, you just handle
the crying scene.
Okay.
I've memorized my lines.
Alright.
Let me check this one.
Eight members pass on
martial-arts power one by one.
Each person must create
an impressive set of combat moves.
After that, you need to pass the power
by touching with body parts
in ascending order from low to high.
The eighth member
shall use their neck
to transfer the martial-art power
onto He's head.
We need to come up with
a set of moves first, right?
It doesn't need to be complicated.
Just this one.
This one.
Very simple, right?
Just pass it secretly.
For example, I can do it like this
once I'm finished.
Start with the foot.
Pass to him.
Just make a big show of it.
But when whispering,
you still look sneaky.
Like this.
(A light touch)
That's what it means, right?
I'll finish with Five-Animal Frolics.
Tiger Fist.
I'm...
Heart gouge.
Okay, that works.
Alright, you take the final turn.
Okay, I'm the last one.
This is prepared for you.
His early-morning kit.
Props.
(De-puffing tool)
What's this?
What's this for?
Ear cleaning.
This is also for ear cleaning.
Let's go.
(Happy to serve He)
Serve the guest. Let's go.
Off to work.
He's probably dozing off from waiting.
He must realize we're messing with him.
I'm telling you.
(Will Chen He figure out
the secret missions?)
We made him wait this long.
He'll definitely catch on
once we walk in.
Hello. He, good morning.
It's already noon, buddy.
(Already on ultra-long standby)
It's noon.
I've been waiting
ever since I got up this morning.
Welcome back to the Earth Group.
The production team prepared
a Good Morning, Princess
welcome ceremony for you.
Here are the rules.
Please check.
Eight members will come to the room
to wake me up.
Sorry.
I'm already up.
(No need to trouble you all)
I've been up for a long time.
(But the princess is still
in a grumpy morning mood)
I lost sleep last night.
Missing everyone.
Within ten minutes,
help me finish brushing my teeth.
I've already brushed my teeth.
(One step late again)
Do styling.
De-puff.
(Is it still necessary?)
Choose an outfit.
A series of morning routines.
Make you the most dazzling
among all members.
Will I still look dazzling
after they're done?
Then take
a departure photo
and send it to AI for judgment.
And to give you
an even more memorable reunion,
the eight members will
also
complete some weird tasks along the way.
(Chen He already knows the members
will carry out secret missions)
And
without being spotted,
I need to
observe their odd movements
as much as possible
and capture footage for evidence.
(Prop: Visual ear pick)
(Equipment testing)
It's my first time using it.
Do you think they will
finish those secret missions
without you noticing?
Probably.
So many against one.
If they can't succeed,
wouldn't they be idiots?
(Who's the Idiot Welcome Ceremony
officially begins)
(Good Morning, Princess Welcome Ceremony
(What kind of look is that?)
Sir.
I've got gout.
Take it out.
Take out what?
You haven't seen me for so long.
No gift for me?
(Just give whatever, morning kit)
This is for you.
Eight people, just one bag?
There are eight inside.
Eight inside.
(Picking out clothes on his own)
Honglei.
(Obsessed)
He's browsing through your clothes.
Honglei.
It's been a while.
What are you doing?
I'm checking out your clothes.
Checking my fashion sense.
Can I pick a couple?
Sure.
Thanks.
Are you giving this to me?
Sure.
(Secretly reminding)
(Do the mission now)
Complete the relay first.
You lost weight.
(Distracting him)
A bit thinner.
All these clothes look great.
(Starting to perform the move)
(Secret Mission 3: Kung Fu Relay)
(First leg: Lin Yi to Gong Jun)
(Relay completed)
(Your turn, bro)
(Got it)
He.
I'm taking these pants.
(Keep distracting)
Okay.
(Second leg: Gong Jun to Li Naiwen)
This is handsome, man.
This looks nice.
Does this come with the pants?
No.
I matched it myself.
(Keeps the move precise)
Who am I talking to?
This looks nice.
Does this come with the pants?
(Relay completed)
No, I matched it myself.
(Third leg: Li Naiwen to Liu Yuning)
He...
He's got a big acting itch.
(Covering)
Like, I quit.
I quit.
Why are you like this?
(Notices)
Yeah.
(Third leg: Li Naiwen to Liu Yuning)
(Something's off)
(Looking for the evidence tool)
Where's my ear pick?
You're a bit puffy today.
(Who asked?)
This looks good.
Yeah.
This blue is good.
(How long are you going to pick?)
Just a white T-shirt on top looks great.
(Hands over the ear pick)
I'm a bit puffy.
This just goes straight into the ear?
(Mind your own business)
What are you saying?
(Block)
What is this?
Don't block my camera, okay?
Move!
(Can they be any more obvious?)
They're surrounding me.
You...
Did you put on makeup?
A little.
Your eyes...
You look so guarded.
What's wrong?
What did we do to you?
(Block)
You're all so...
Look at you, so terrified.
Don't block my camera. Move!
(Innocent)
I'm relying on this one camera now.
I'm telling you.
(The last remaining close-up camera)
And this is filming from below.
Let me put this one in front of you.
Time to get your hair and makeup done.
How about this?
Let's divide the work.
Hurry up and...
Get him ready.
Do his makeup.
Let's print a photo of Daniel Wu
and stick it on his face, okay?
(What does that mean?)
Look.
What?
How is He any worse than Daniel Wu?
I'm still a bit behind.
(Just a bit behind)
Daniel Wu...
I never lose.
(My confidence is undefeated)
You're way handsomer than him.
You're Daniel Six.
[*"Wu" sounds like "Five" in Chinese]
Not funny.
That joke was a bit lame.
(All looks, no brains)
Sorry.
Let's just freshen up.
Let's go.
Find a place with a mirror.
(Blind spot)
Here.
Here, come on.
He.
We've already found a place for makeup.
We found it.
All set.
I have makeup on.
Let's do your hair.
Do your hair and tidy up.
Here, sit down, man.
Sit.
I need to wash my hair, right?
Wash your hair.
What's wrong?
(Feeling something's off)
You guys
have a mission, right?
Yes.
(Can we say that?)
You have a mission?
Yes, really.
We're going to make you
look your absolute best.
(Go ahead, I'm watching)
So, man, hurry in.
We're running out of time.
What are you doing?
Hurry up, man.
(Trying to pull him away)
Stop dawdling, hurry.
He.
(Seizing the chance to do the mission)
He, I will help you with your outfit.
Just this set.
(Fourth leg: Liu Yuning to Chen Xingxu,
Relay completed)
Okay, I like this set.
Let's go.
(Fifth leg: Chen Xingxu to Sun Honglei)
(Sixth leg: Sun Honglei to Wang Yuwen)
Okay, come.
Wash your face?
(Trap)
(Not falling for it)
It's hard not to be on guard with you.
You're from Go Fighting,
and you're doing something like this.
(Forcing)
Come on, please sit.
(Sixth leg: Sun Honglei to Wang Yuwen)
(Seventh leg: Wang Yuwen to Guo Jingfei)
(Only the last leg left)
Touch his head with your neck.
(Can this difficult move fool Chen He?)
My neck touches his head?
Yeah.
You really...
You really have lost weight.
Let me
compare faces...
Let me compare faces with him.
(Taking the chance to get closer)
Who does that from behind?
Let me stretch my chin first.
(Naturally sticks close)
Mine is smaller.
(Secret Mission 3: Kung Fu Relay done)
(Gives a look)
Where's the depuffing thing?
Which one?
The one in the fridge.
In the fridge.
Lin Yi.
Lin Yi, I think...
I think...
(Do we pretend to do high jump?)
Can you reach here?
(Secret Mission 1: Basketball)
Two need to pass the ball back and forth
twice in the living room
and pass the ball to where He is.
I can't.
You can't reach it?
(The two take the chance
to complete the basketball mission)
(Oblivious)
What do we do?
That's easy.
Just a little styling.
(Silent scream)
(You win with your height)
Quick.
(Enduring the pain to continue)
(Secret Mission 1:
Mime Kung-Fu Ball Games: Basketball)
For Lin Yi.
(One-handed dribble)
Go.
(Knee slide in advance)
In front of him.
(The final step:
dunking in front of Chen He)
(Doing this in front of me?)
Can this also help me?
Can this help reduce the swelling?
We weren't like this when we were young.
Right?
We...
We've come this far
maybe because we don't do this.
(Saw it)
(Secret Mission 1:
Mime Kung-Fu Ball Games: Basketball)
(Knee slide celebration move)
Verify it.
(Secret Mission 1:
Mime Kung-Fu Ball Games: Basketball done)
He.
How about I get you
a hairstyle like Fei's?
American quiff.
Why don't we take a walk
to the bathroom?
(Making an excuse to stand up)
Bathroom.
Where's the bathroom?
(Secret Mission 2: Reenact a TV drama)
Three members need to go to He's room,
change into Bad Lei style outfits
and reenact a classic quarrel scene.
(Famous scene)
This outfit is pretty nice.
(People get busy when they're awkward)
Yeah, it's pretty...
It's pretty trendy.
What's going on here?
Yuwen, what's with the outfit change?
(Keeps recording)
This one.
This one is for you.
(Quick thinking)
Will I be the coolest if I wear this?
I'm putting together
your outfit for today.
You have to wear their clothes today.
(Pretty good at covering up)
What outfit did you put together for me?
OOTD.
(Afraid to make eye contact)
Listen, Gong Jun.
When you lie,
you can't even look me in the eye,
and you start shaking.
(Guilty)
I'm not shaking.
(Pretending to pass by casually)
Don't you walk away!
Are you afraid to face me?
What are you doing?
Where did you get these pants?
(Rock music festival? Studs, drawstrings,
leopard print, patchwork style, flowy fur)
You're asking? I found them.
And you?
These pants.
(Hip-hop melon style)
If you weren't forced to,
you would never wear them.
No, I'm doing it willingly.
They said we're playing some game here.
They were worried
my dress wasn't convenient.
Is it a game
about dressing up like an idiot?
No.
An idiot?
(Isn't this fashionable?)
An idiot.
Really?
Of course.
Why don't you try it on?
Isn't it a team battle?
We just want to look a little cooler.
These two pieces go quite well together.
Now that's just nonsense.
(A hot mess)
Tell me.
Go take a look in the mirror.
This is really nice.
You guys...
You guys were just playing basketball.
What?
(Recording)
(The brain is going crazy)
What's wrong?
What did she say?
She wants to put makeup on you.
Makeup.
Can you seriously learn some Cantonese?
It's been over a year.
(Crisis averted)
A whole year and no progress.
Come on.
What do we do?
Oh, no.
(Seen through)
He already knows.
It's fine.
No.
At most, he thinks
we're trying to steal
the spotlight from the AI.
We want to look better than him.
But he won't think
there's anything wrong with us.
Let's go to the bathroom to dress up.
Let's...
dress up openly
and then do the scene, okay?
(A good attitude
determines an actor's life)
Good.
(Lin's American quiff)
His hair's easy.
Chen He.
He's got great potential,
great head shape, and great face shape.
What else?
Great.
Chen He.
(Very pleased by the flattery)
Great head shape.
Great potential.
Great hairstyle.
That's me, the three-great guy.
Hurry up.
No one's looking. Hurry up.
(Chen He was taken to another room)
Hurry up.
(Secret Mission 2: Reenact a TV drama)
(Starts acting immediately)
Isn't everything I do now
all for the kid?
You just got back and now start arguing?
(Front-row seats)
Not eating.
Just arguing every single day.
Well, Mom.
Just eat your food.
Mind your own business.
Can you speak Mandarin?
This is my son.
What's wrong with me speaking
in my hometown dialect
with my son?
Cry now.
Cry.
(Working up tears)
(No tears, no success)
Cry.
(Making him cry)
Okay.
Go on.
You are always picking fights.
What's wrong with me speaking
a little Wuhan dialect to my son?
Just speaking my mom's hometown dialect.
Is it really that serious?
Who is my mom doing all this for?
(Can't cry)
She...
She doesn't like speaking Mandarin.
You can speak the Sichuan dialect.
Problem solved.
You can even speak French.
As for the Sichuan dialect,
what's so hard about it?
This is easy.
(Changing the subject)
This is kind of interesting.
What's wrong?
They're speaking their hometown dialect.
(Sees through)
Any personal preferences, man?
Anything's fine.
Mr. Lin, I'm fine with whatever.
Yi's got some skills.
He's really skilled.
It looks great with barely any effort.
All thanks to your great haircut.
(Been recording all along)
(Secret Mission 2: Reenact a TV drama)
Cry now.
Cry.
(While the tears are still wet)
You're making them dry.
The tears are coming.
Push them out.
Push.
Okay.
(Secret Mission 2: Reenact a TV drama done)
Take it off.
Next mission.
Done.
Let me do it.
He.
Your hair looks so good.
Lin Yi did a pretty good job.
Pretty good. Not bad.
Really not bad.
(Checking the tool)
A bit retro.
If you're not happy with anything,
you can fix it yourself.
Are you happy with this outfit?
Here, look at the pants.
Okay.
Show him the T-shirt.
Pair it with this plain white T-shirt.
No problem.
Change your clothes first.
(The ear pick is taken away)
Otherwise, your hair...
(Evidence collection tool lost)
You should change first.
Okay.
Go change.
(Changing clothes)
(Where is Wang Yuwen going?)
(Secret Mission 1: Mime Human Bowling)
One member will mime bowling.
The rest split into three rows
and act out getting knocked over
and falling down.
Come over here. We're missing one.
Who?
You bowl.
(The ear pick taken from Chen He's hand)
(It has recorded the whole process)
Coming.
One, two, three, go.
(A single pin left standing)
Because usually one pin never falls.
I'm the one.
(Quite true to life)
It didn't hit me.
(The rule requires everyone to fall)
Everyone has to fall.
Come on.
I fell late.
Okay, we can wrap this up.
Done.
(Rehearsal over,
get ready for the real deal)
(Outfit change complete)
To be honest,
the outfit Honglei picked out
is exactly what my stylist would pair.
It's really good.
(Satisfied)
But don't you think it needs...?
It's a bit empty here.
It needs to be shiny.
Is my hair done or not?
Not done.
It's not done yet.
Fix it.
Yeah.
Fix his hair.
He just put on clothes.
Re-style it for him.
Yeah, it wasn't set just now.
It has to be in front of him, right?
(Remaining unfinished secret mission:
Human Bowling)
This is a bit difficult.
Come on.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
You're welcome.
(What kind of Cantonese is that?)
Where did my ear pick go?
(Looking for the tool)
(Only one last Human Bowling mission)
Then we...
Well...
He.
He, just wait a moment.
We need to prepare over here
to welcome your entrance.
You're choreographing a dance.
(I know you guys are on a mission)
Just a little preparation.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
Come on.
Let me use it a bit more.
(Taking back the ear pick)
Is my outfit okay, He?
Very good.
We're going to act out
being blown away by his handsomeness,
by his looks.
Let's work on your entrance.
Come on.
Just walk out handsomely in a moment,
and that's it.
I'll come out with Chen He.
No need.
Because I need to...
(Responsible for the bowling action)
I need to...
Just throw He out here.
Blow us all away.
Get ready. Get ready.
(I'm ready)
Okay, close the door.
Come on.
Just follow behind me.
There's a very handsome...
(Sees through it but leaves it unsaid)
What are you going to do?
What are you guys going to do?
(Guilty)
Nothing.
I'm not pranking you.
Yeah, as soon as he comes out, we say,
"So handsome!"
And we just fall down. That's it.
We faint from his handsomeness.
Yeah.
Come on.
Come out.
I'll be behind you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here he is,
the most handsome one,
Chen He!
- So handsome!
I'm going to faint!
So handsome!
(Bro, fall down now)
I'm going to faint!
I'm dazzled by your handsomeness.
We have to fall, right?
(Could you be more dramatic?)
So handsome!
I'm going to faint!
I'm dazzled!
Okay.
(Applause for our acting)
So handsome!
(I've recorded everything)
So dazzling!
(Cheer, idiots)
(Acting blinded)
So bright!
Chen He!
- Chen He!
Are we taking photos yet?
Did you take the photo?
Come on. Take the photo.
(Mission success if AI judges Chen He)
Take a departure photo.
(As the most dazzling among the nine)
I'll let the AI judge it.
Take the photo.
Let's just
pass it in one go, okay?
One shot.
Come on.
Everyone, remember to cover your faces
or make ugly faces.
Wait a second.
I've been dressed up for so long.
Do I really need you
to cover your faces to win?
(Harsh words hurt He's heart)
He, just in case.
You can show your face.
(Someone he's confident he can beat)
Okay, let's do it this way.
We have two chances anyway, okay?
For the first time,
we'll just act normal.
We'll see what the AI says.
Okay.
See how the AI judges it.
See its standards.
Alright, three, two, one.
Wait.
Reveal the results later.
Can we take the second one first?
Okay, come on.
Let's take the silly one first.
Smart. Okay.
Come on.
You don't make a silly face.
I won't make a silly face.
I definitely won't.
Alright, ready...
Two, one.
(Friendly reminder:
You can take a screenshot)
(AI analyzing)
First, this is our normal photo,
without any
ugly faces.
What is the AI's comment?
(Will Chen He be the most dazzling
in the group photo?)
The AI comment says,
"In this group photo,
the man in the front row center,
who wears a white T-shirt, plaid pants,
and colorful bead necklaces,
is visually the most dazzling person."
(AI verified)
We didn't even make ugly faces.
He won without us making ugly faces.
"This gentleman in the plaid shirt
has an outfit with a strong contrast
and personal style.
His relaxed vibe is off the charts.
He is the visual anchor
of the entire photo,
radiating a natural variety show comedic
and core-leading aura."
(calling out your ID number)
That's quite a compliment.
There's another one saying,
besides the most dazzling person,
everyone else is erased.
The one left is He.
Double verified.
Okay.
(Told you I'm only a bit
behind Daniel Wu)
Can you say something real?
(Let AI give a sharp review)
Say some truth.
Yeah.
Okay.
Come on. Read it out.
Come on.
Since we want it a bit sharper,
let's skip the pleasantries.
"The most dazzling person
is the man in the front center,
white T-shirt and plaid pants.
He is forcing a debut as the center."
(Forcing a debut as the center)
Forcing the center position.
(Gaudy)
A gaudy bead necklace with plaid pants.
Gaudy...
He's even clutching a plush toy.
He looks exactly like
someone visiting during the New Year,
who insists on wearing something new
and ending up as the attention-seeker."
(Yuanbao is going crazy)
That's harsh.
"He has the relaxed vibe,
(Keep commenting)
but it's indeed too visually messy.
As if he's afraid people won't know
he's the core of the hype squad."
(Stop it)
I think that's enough.
Do you want to read other comments?
See? You said,
"Do you want to read other comments?"
Don't you want to hear yours?
Read his.
"The man in the tennis shirt,
a classic neighborhood workout grandpa."
(Classic neighborhood workout grandpa)
He broke down!
So arrogant!
I knew it was going to be harsh,
but I didn't expect it to be this harsh.
I'm not even close with Yuanbao.
(This AI has no sense of boundaries)
"The man in black...
The man in black."
Fei.
"His gaze is sharp,
but his stance is stiff.
He looks like an executive
who was forced
to accompany his boss
to a team-building event."
(Well-known executive, Guo Jingfei)
This is better than Nai's, anyway.
I'm workout grandpa.
Better than Nai's.
The most brutal so far is yours.
He.
It's really not mine.
Mine is actually okay.
He has it the worst.
(Only the workout grandpa is hurt)
I think the workout grandpa...
How did I end up as a workout grandpa?
What's wrong with being gaudy?
I just like it.
Is it because of this?
(Even starting to analyze)
No.
It's talking about the soul
and the aura.
(The soul and aura
have been like an "uncle")
Look. Don't analyze
this issue seriously.
It's because of his polo.
Polo.
And your outfit is way too simple.
Looks like a gym outfit?
You're the one giving the sharp reviews.
Did we complete the mission?
Yes, everyone.
But,
He,
in the part just now,
they actually
completed three hidden missions.
(Didn't expect that, huh?)
I wonder if you can guess them.
His brain is already fried.
All sorts of...
(Too many suspicious behaviors)
He definitely doesn't know
what our missions are.
He can't guess.
(Confident)
Well...
Three, right?
Yes.
These two guys shooting hoops next to me
were a bit off.
(The basketball duo was guessed first)
Impressive.
Also, when I was taking photos,
you and someone
most likely
did an interactive move
behind me.
Probably.
There are more.
There are more?
We had one...
We had one that was perfect.
He really...
That's right.
Couldn't feel it. Yeah.
Okay.
That was when I walked out,
(Human Bowling mission discovered)
everyone did a move together.
Yes, that was it.
That one...
It was a bit over the top.
It was a bit too over the top.
A bit too over the top.
These are the weird things, anyway.
Okay.
So He not only discovered your missions,
he even took evidence of you.
You also had a mission?
Sorry.
It was actually my ear pick.
So you were holding it
the whole time just now, right?
After I took his ear pick,
he asked for it back.
Yeah, I was wondering
where my ear pick went.
Impressive.
The real winner of this round is He.
(Good Morning, Princess
Welcome Ceremony Winner: Chen He)
Awesome.
Let him win.
A win for everyone is the real win.
♪Only by fighting can you win♪
(Cold meme, late but still here)
Okay. Come on.
Next, we're about to start
our official trip.
Sichuan has a calling card to the world,
the adorable national treasure,
giant panda.
Po from the movie Kung Fu Panda,
is based on those from Sichuan
both in appearance and movement.
Today, we're not just taking you all
to unlock this name card
of Chengdu up close,
but we're also
letting you personally enter
the world of fast-paced grudges
where Po lives.
(Addicted to the ear pick)
Experience a journey
that is free, easy,
(Jawline on display)
relaxed, and comfortable.
So cool.
So, everyone,
let's go see the pandas!
Xiongmer, right?
[*Means panda in Sichuan dialect]
In Sichuan dialect.
Xiongmer.
Xiongmao.
(Sichuan dialect, get)
Xiongmer.
That won't do, right?
I like it.
As if drenched by rain,
sour and refreshing.
That won't do, right?
I like it.
As if bursting with power,
full of texture.
That won't do, right?
I like it.
As if being soulmates,
addictive.
Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon.
I like it.
Chengdu is so great.
So chill.
(Heading to the Chengdu Research Base)
We're so lucky
(of Giant Panda Breeding)
to actually catch
this kind of weather in July
here in Chengdu.
It's really comfortable.
You can at least say a little
about pandas, right?
So nice.
They have huge appetites,
and are so cute.
I just love their chill lifestyle.
It really represents Chengdu.
It's about everyone enjoying life,
not arrogant or restless at all.
What they embody is a kind of silence.
Look.
(Silence)
I'm now imagining
what it would feel like
to be a panda.
Silence.
Close your eyes, and you are the panda.
Yeah.
We're here.
(Chengdu Research Base
of Giant Panda Breeding)
Let's go, Nai.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to our panda base.
Miss, what's your surname?
My surname is Li.
Hello, Miss Li.
You can all call me Nana.
Nana.
Miss Nana.
(Nana, Docent at the base)
A very warm welcome
to our Chengdu Research Base
of Giant Panda Breeding.
So next up,
I will lead you all
to find
our adorably healing giant pandas.
Okay.
Let's go.
The area we are currently in
is actually a new zone
of our panda base.
Our entire panda base
covers a total area
of 588 acres.
The new zone here is over 300 acres,
and the old zone over there
is over 150 mu.
Currently, at our panda base,
there are about 270-plus giant pandas.
Yes.
The current global population
of captive giant pandas
is a total
of 808.
But our base alone
has more than 270.
Giant pandas have existed in this world
for at least 8 million years.
They are our national treasure,
and a gem for the world.
Today, you can
see the long-awaited giant pandas here.
How old is Huahua, Miss?
Huahua
is already six years old this year.
(I'm six years old)
Six years old.
She just had her sixth birthday.
Yes.
A panda's age is...
As for their age...
Their maximum lifespan.
Actually, wild giant pandas
can live to about 18 to 20 years old.
(Wild giant panda lifespan:
Approximately 18-20 years)
Under captive conditions,
their lifespan is a bit longer,
reaching 25 to 30.
(Captive giant panda lifespan:
Approximately 25-30 years)
The longest-lived one
reached 38 years old.
Yes.
One panda year is equivalent
to about three to three and a half
of our human years.
Multiply by three to three and a half.
That's right.
Later today,
you'll be able to see
one of our older giant pandas
in this area.
Today, we have
two very essential spots.
On the left is our Xinghan Hall.
(Xinghan Hall, a hub of exhibition,
education, interaction, and culture)
After the visit
to Xinghan Hall,
we will go to Xingxing Delivery Room.
Okay.
Next, let's enter
the indoor area from the left side.
Look.
There.
This is the oldest giant panda
I just mentioned
in our area.
25?
Yes, 25 years old.
Almost 25 years old.
That's like 75 human years.
Almost there.
So cute.
You can really see a bit of age.
The fur color, maybe.
His name is Xiong Bang.
It's actually
having some apples
fed to it by our keeper.
Actually,
as for the diet of giant pandas,
you can all guess
what do they mainly eat?
Bamboo.
Yes.
- The bamboo, bamboo leaves, and bamboo stalks in front of us.
- Bamboo, apple
and bamboo shoot.
Yes.
They also eat meat, right?
Actually, captive giant pandas
do not eat meat.
(Footage sourced online)
We provide them
with these multigrain steamed buns.
Steamed buns.
To supplement the trace elements
and vitamins their bodies need.
Look. Every day, they also eat a bit
of fresh vegetables and fruits.
Apples
are a very popular
supplementary food for them.
Sweet.
Yes.
Because their intestines
are very short,
food doesn't really linger inside
before getting excreted.
So pandas
can only constantly eat
and sleep
to store their energy.
In terms of height,
looking at them like this,
you might not think they're very tall.
You can all guess
roughly how tall they are
when they stand up.
1.87 meters.
1.86 meters.
1.9 meters.
2 meters.
Yuning, how tall are you?
I'm 1.9 meters.
Then about the same.
Maybe.
Yes, about the same as you.
Around 1.8 to 1.9 meters.
Really?
Yes.
(I'm a 1.9-meter sweet college boy)
They can weigh
up to about 100 to 150 kilograms.
He doesn't look 1.9 meters.
Looks about my height.
They look so soft and adorable to us.
Yes, super cute.
But actually,
their bite force is incredibly strong.
They also have powerful, muscular limbs
and razor-sharp claws.
So for pandas,
in the wild, they basically
have no natural predators to speak of.
They are bears.
Yeah, they belong to the bear family.
Pandas have no predators.
Then why are they
so rare now?
Well, for giant pandas,
breeding is extremely difficult.
There are three major challenges.
First, they have trouble mating.
(Breeding challenge 1: Hard to mate)
A panda's mating cycle
is only about a week long per year.
And when it comes to choosing a partner,
they are extremely picky.
Then,
female pandas also
have a very hard time conceiving.
(2. Female panda's hard to conceive)
A female panda's fertile window
might be just about two days a year.
Two days?
Yes.
So that window is absolutely critical.
And third,
raising the cubs is incredibly tough.
(3. Hard to raise giant panda cubs)
Can you guess
what the panda cubs look like
when they're first born?
Pink.
"Little mice."
Yes, you're right.
(Newborn panda cub)
Right?
They look just like little mice.
They're pink,
with a layer
of sparse white fuzz on top.
They weigh
about 100 to 120 grams,
which is one-thousandth
of their mother's weight.
Have you seen online
that video of a cub scaring a panda?
No.
I've seen it. It's hilarious.
I'll have to look it up later.
It's so funny.
(The cub's sudden squeal
froze its mom mid-bite)
Its own baby.
It's so interesting.
Such a goof.
Okay, next,
in the neighboring enclosure,
you can take a look,
and let's try to find...
It's up there.
It's trying to climb down.
That one's the cutest.
Look at this one.
Is it sleeping?
Yeah, it's asleep.
Sleeping like that?
It looks like it's about to fall.
Half its body is hanging off the edge.
If it's not careful,
it'll fall right off.
Before,
at the old facility,
the one for pandas.
The old park,
also in Chengdu.
There was one about that size,
sitting on a very thin branch.
It looked so cool.
Just perched up there.
And then it just fell off.
It was hanging there, so cute.
So adorable.
We just mentioned
how tall pandas are.
Come on. Let's compare,
everyone.
1.80 meters.
Come on. Take a look.
Who's taller, you or the panda?
Well, with my shoes on,
I'm taller than it.
This isn't quite 1.80 meters.
Because we usually see them
either sitting or lying down,
we might think they aren't that tall.
We're all taller than them.
You want to touch a real one, right?
You want to see what they feel like.
(Poop from eating bamboo leaves)
Can you all guess
what panda poop actually smells like?
Like plants.
You got it.
Actually,
it has a fresh bamboo aroma.
Inside their droppings,
there's a lot of bamboo fiber.
We can recycle it,
(Panda poop aids scientific monitoring)
using it to make paper
(Paper, fertilizer, or souvenirs)
or turning it into fertilizer.
Okay.
Alright. Right this way, please.
Okay, we're about to arrive
at our Xingxing Delivery Room.
(Giant Panda Xingxing Delivery Room)
So in a moment,
we can see the mother
with the panda cubs in their enclosure.
Little cubs.
Up ahead, we have a panda cub
climbing down a tree.
Yeah.
We see it.
So cute.
So adorable.
This little one
hangs out in this tree all day.
Look, quick.
It's so cute.
How old is this little cub?
One year old.
This cub here
is almost one year old.
What a tiny little thing.
So cute.
Yeah, it's so small.
This one is too cute.
We can't be loud, right?
Right.
Volume,
double the volume.
It might think we're some kind of beast.
(Panda head, big satisfaction)
What's it fiddling with over there?
It's been doing that all day.
What's it messing with?
Right now, it's probably
playing with some grass
or a small twig.
Because at this stage,
it still drinks its mother's milk.
Drinks mother's milk.
Mother's milk and formula from a basin.
Drinks formula from a basin?
That's so cute.
(Drinking bottled milk)
So precious.
And it won't be weaned until
about one and a half to two years old.
So it's used to humans.
Only the keepers can interact with them.
Of course.
No one else can.
So its butt even works like a radar.
Too cute.
I have to take a picture.
It's so cute.
(You're mesmerized by me, aren't you?)
Oh, my God.
It's so...
Just so comfortable.
It's waving hello.
Hi.
It's making a phone call.
Don't bother it.
(A little humor)
Kids shouldn't play with phones.
Look at that little paw.
And it has this too.
It even waved.
This is for real.
This kid is just too cute.
Let's go.
(Can't hold a smile back)
Go.
(See you next time)
Everyone,
come over here,
and let's look for our panda.
Look,
on the right perch, do you see it?
Yeah.
It's a really tiny one.
Another little one.
There's a panda cub over here,
and a panda mother.
Another tiny little thing.
A little cub, another one.
Look at this panda mother.
Her name is Zhenxi.
This is her first time being a mom.
She actually has a very strong
maternal instinct.
When we come by,
she's often here with her twins,
lying on this perch,
nursing both cubs at the same time.
Taking care of the cubs
is an demanding task for a panda mother.
It usually lasts 18 months.
Actually, inside this enclosure,
if you look around, you can see
a cave-like structure in the back.
For pandas,
in the wild,
they would choose a spacious
tree hollow or rock cave as their den.
Yes, this is also part of our
environmental enrichment design.
Look, it's coming out.
Yeah.
So chubby.
This one is so funny.
Look at the way it walks,
swinging its butt side to side.
Its front and back paws
both point inward when it walks.
In the wild, actually,
it's very convenient
for moving through dense forests.
So, panda
also has the nickname
Hermit of the Bamboo Forest.
Because of this walking posture,
it can minimize the noise it makes.
Every giant panda
has a unique set of eye patches.
Their eye patches are like
our human fingerprints,
with each one having some differences.
And pandas can also make
over a dozen different vocalizations,
each conveying a different meaning.
On the path of conservation today,
China carried out ex-situ and in-situ
conservation for pandas,
establishing zoos and nature reserves.
So, thanks to the
tireless efforts
of panda researchers,
the International Union
for Conservation of Nature
has downgraded
the giant panda's threat status
from Endangered to Vulnerable in 2016.
(ID Card)
(Vulnerable VU)
That's amazing.
Okay.
Our panda tour today
ends here.
Please visit Chengdu often
to see our pandas.
Thank you.
(Wow The World S2)
I think those with kids
should bring them to see this.
Exactly.
Pandas are really just
too cute.
(Two satisfied faces)
It's so therapeutic.
It heals the soul.
I remember that song.
What was it called?
♪Mimi lies in her mother's arms♪
♪Counting the stars♪
Who sang that again?
Cheng Lin.
Cheng Lin, right.
See?
We're truly from the same generation.
Two workout grandpas.
(Both strong and healthy)
♪Stars, oh stars♪
♪So beautiful♪
♪Tomorrow's breakfast♪
♪Where is it?♪
♪Please let me♪
♪Protect you♪
♪Just like I protect myself♪
It was so popular back then.
(Chengdu Panda Base Sightseeing Tower,
inspired by bamboo shoots.)
This is the Panda Tower.
This tower looks like a bamboo shoot.
Kung fu.
Come to the front.
Let's go over here.
(Golden Blade Drawn Fist
known as Greenwood Small Hand.)
(It focuses on close-quarters combat,)
(fully displays the chivalry and power
of Sichuan native martial arts.)
There's a big event here.
(Qingcheng Tai Chi, a core component
of Qingcheng martial arts.)
(It is one of the few Tai Chi styles
originating from the southwest region.)
(Tai Chi camera movement)
Want to add some more flair?
That's so cool.
This master
even brought such a young kid.
(Li Lezhen, three-time champion of Sichuan
Children's Martial Arts Competition)
Okay.
(Liu Suibin, the head of Qingcheng Sect)
Hello, everyone.
I'm Liu Suibin,
the head of the Qingcheng Sect.
The prototype for Po's martial arts moves
in Kung Fu Panda,
a national inheritor
of Qingcheng martial arts,
the president of Sichuan Martial Arts
Culture Research Association,
and the head of the Qingcheng Sect,
Mr. Liu.
Hi, Mr. Liu.
Today, Master Liu has brought
a unique skill of the Qingcheng Sect.
In a bit, he can show it
to everyone.
Okay?
Okay.
Come on, take the stage.
(Luo Liangyou, Qingcheng Sect disciple)
He'll perform.
Look at that glass.
He can crush it with his finger.
The finger skill.
Yeah.
Come on.
Everyone, give it a try.
That's a regular tea cup.
Flick it hard
and see if you can shatter it.
The real deal.
So, you'll shatter it with your finger?
Yes.
Like this?
(Shatter a glass with a finger)
Using your Qi.
My hand hurts so much.
I think so too.
My fingernail hurts.
Oh my.
(Impressed)
It shattered.
Impressive.
It's pulverized.
There's more.
Want to give it a try?
It's very light.
Let's do it.
Where should I flick it?
You can flick it here.
If you're feeling good,
you can flick this one.
But
be careful.
Should I use my fingernail?
Use your fingernail.
Fingernail.
Grip it tight.
Don't let the cup fly away.
Use force.
(Looks painful)
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
Come on, it was pretty loud.
But it's not...
It looks like it cracked a little.
Just by force?
Jun.
Did you crack a little,
or did it crack a little?
One more flick and it'll shatter.
Because of the resonance.
(A bit of talent)
Are you also from Qingcheng Sect?
(People from Chengdu can fly)
It's in his blood. He's a native.
As expected
of a local.
(Envious)
Lin Yi, your turn.
Don't...
Don't flick that one.
It hurts.
This one is actually harder.
This one is harder.
This one feels sturdy.
It's short.
Why did it become round?
Is a round one easy?
It's easy.
They're all the same,
I think.
Which part did Jun flick?
Flick the edge.
From the inside, outwards.
You have to use your fingernail.
This...
(Becoming a trainer)
Here.
Jun is already teaching.
This is the spot, right?
Yeah.
Because this one is round,
flicking anywhere is the same.
Right.
Exactly what you'd expect from a local.
Can you go lower?
It won't hit you.
(Who stepped on Yi's tail?)
My finger's already red.
It really hurts a bit.
This is quite hard.
Master,
do all Chengdu locals know this trick?
Alright, that's it.
Thank you, Master.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Master.
Today, Master Liu has come to our set,
and among all of you, he'd like to find
a junior
for Po from Kung Fu Panda
and Lezhen.
We'd be junior brothers.
You'd have to call her
- Senior Lezhen.
- Senior.
(Young age but high seniority)
(With respect)
Hello, Senior.
Hello.
No.
Don't.
(Gently refused)
No.
She said no.
So next up,
we'll have a few rounds of challenges.
In each upcoming round,
the winning member
will receive a thread of true energy
from the Qingcheng Sect.
(True energy of Qingcheng Sect)
The member who collects two threads
will become the "Kung Fu Panda"
and win
the Supreme Treasure of the Sect
prepared by Master Liu.
(Supreme Treasure of Qingcheng Sect)
So everyone,
for the chance to become
Lezhen's junior,
let's all head down to the first floor
and get ready for the first round.
Everyone, let's move.
Okay.
(What kind of look is this?)
Got one leg crossed over.
My gout is acting up, dear friends.
I'm not being putting on airs.
With Honglei
and Naiwen here,
I wouldn't dare.
What if they weren't here?
If they weren't here,
you'd be putting on airs?
(Hard to hold back)
I see.
Well,
my gout flared up.
I've been standing this whole time,
and all the blood from my brain
has rushed to my feet.
Now I need the blood to flow back.
Okay.
Growing up,
we all definitely had a phase
of watching martial arts films,
including TV shows and movies.
So,
there are always many classic scenes
that we can't forget.
Especially at some critical moments,
the way companions
help each other out has impressed us.
For example,
in Legend of the Condor Heroes,
(A Scene from Legend of the Condor Heroes)
Hong Qigong inspired Guo Jing.
In Kung Fu,
the beggar gave the boy
that secret manual.
(A Scene from Kung Fu)
Those obsessed with the martial world
understand
the unspoken trust and chemistry best.
So, today, we'll do a challenge
that tests both your knowledge
of the martial arts world
and your chemistry with each other.
It's called
Yarn-Spinning Time.
Yarn-Spinning.
What does Yarn-Spinning mean?
(Traditional Cultural Activities in Sichuan and Chongqing)
Yarn-Spinning means chatting.
Chatting.
Just chatting?
That suits us best.
It suits you best, right now.
With your feet kicked up.
All you need is a cup of covered tea.
(Chengdu)
What tea?
Covered tea.
He said you need
a cup
of covered tea.
A cup of tea.
(Same tongue slip)
Need a cup of covered tea.
Covered tea.
It's a tongue twister.
(Tongue twister)
Need a cup of covered tea.
Do you add the "er" sound?
Right.
(Facial muscle practice)
Need a cup of covered tea.
"Covered".
(Detailed)
Add the "er" sound.
It's easier with the "er" sound.
What are you guys doing?
We're playing a game.
Just warming up our lips.
(Follow me)
Need a cup of covered tea.
(Follow)
In a moment, you'll form your groups.
(Free team-forming, one team of four and one of five)
One team of four and one of five.
For each round,
each team sends two members
to act out a scenario.
You'll follow the given situation
and character relationships.
During the performance, guess two lines
and two specific actions,
and then act them out.
The rest of the team will be the guides.
The guides can not only
step in to give hints,
but can also, during the performance,
use "Hey" or "Hmm"
to guide the actors.
After a guide steps in,
once the bell rings, they must stop
and exit the stage.
In the end, the team whose guides
stepped in fewer times
wins.
They'll receive a thread of true energy
from the Qingcheng Sect.
He.
You're finally back.
You pick the teams.
Choose your teammates.
That doesn't sound like a good thing.
I'm telling you,
for this round,
(The guide steps in)
we've got to split up
Wang Yuwen and Liu Yuning.
(Absolutely cannot be in the same team)
Because they're both good at guessing.
If they're together, it'll be too fast.
You two pick.
No, they already said
to let you choose, He.
I already used it.
Did you not understand what I said?
I've already given you your mission.
Do you understand?
You two do rock-paper-scissors.
Your power isn't that great.
Then I'll stand up
and ask for it.
(Humble power holder: Okay)
Just pick four people.
Best to split Lin Yi away too.
Split me away?
(Tear Lin Yi apart?)
We'll play in three groups.
(Did I agree?)
Listen.
Don't let
(The guide steps in again)
Wang Yuwen and Lin Yi be on the same team.
(Why?)
So, I can't be on a team with him
nor him?
(Giving directions)
These two can be on a team.
Stop talking, I'm in charge.
(Any respect?)
Really.
Whose power is it?
I'm just giving a suggestion.
Sit down, now.
Fine.
Come on.
Xingxu,
Lin Yi,
Jun.
(Chen He's team and Wang Yuwen's team)
(Surprised)
Those two with me?
(Can't bear watching)
You just can't stop talking, can you?
You're so brave, you know that?
No, the key is,
he got the most abstract one on his team.
(Abstract)
I'm with those three.
I get him.
They're very abstract.
Even if I lose,
my loss is
totally understandable.
That's so evil.
You've thought of an excuse, huh?
We'll just play four against five.
Don't explain it to them.
Enough talking.
No explanation, just bring it on.
It's fine, you don't have
the manual
and the instructions for Lin Yi.
You wouldn't understand him anyway.
A manual?
How about this? Yuwen goes over,
and you guys go first.
(Holding Lin Yi's manual)
Trading a person for the order?
No, let's just do rock-paper-scissors.
Why trade a person?
Make them regret
not picking you.
Trust him.
If all else fails,
we'll speak in Northeastern dialect.
Alright.
Okay, that's it.
Come on, let's start.
Okay, come on.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Xingxu, Xingxu will do it.
He's never lost.
(Nai's choice)
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
He's never lost.
Rock, paper...
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Lose)
Okay, you go first.
Nice.
Good.
Best of three, right?
(Getting smart)
We can do that.
Go for the win.
(Anxious)
Go.
Okay, I'll play you the second round.
(The winner is playing again)
I'll go.
It's okay.
I've never lost at rock-paper-scissors.
Not in this life.
That's good.
(Feeling threatened)
I'm getting serious. Come on.
Go.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Lost)
(Has some skills)
Come on, the deciding round.
(Lost)
(I hate this)
Which round did you not lose?
Hello.
(Hello. Bad signal)
Come on, let's officially start.
(Are you okay?)
Officially start?
Get out of here.
Just get up there already.
You just have to get in on everything.
Get up there.
Come on. Get up there.
Okay, you go first.
I want to see how amazing you five are.
Four and a half.
(One, two, three, half, four)
Four and a half? That's so hurtful.
Let's see what the prompt is first.
(Preset scenario)
After years in the martial world,
a pair of ill-fated,
gravely injured twins.
You guess.
Someone has to guess, right?
Us two.
(Liu Yuning and Guo Jingfei perform)
Let it be us two.
Let Honglei describe it.
(Sun Honglei, Wang Yuwen and Li Naiwen,
Guides)
Okay.
(Guides checking the question)
(Looking troubled)
(Actions 1: Suck out poisoned blood
2: Face-to-face energy healing)
(Lines 1: I'm in so much pain
2: Qi deviation)
Let them act first.
(Preset scenario: Severely-injured twins
who have been in the martial world for years)
My younger brother.
Brother.
Where are you hurt?
I've hurt
my fingernail.
Fingernail.
Paronychia.
Brother.
I'm hurt inside.
We're going too slowly.
What do we do?
Run faster.
Okay.
But my foot is injured.
I can't run.
Carry me.
It's the toenail.
My brother, I'm down to one leg now.
(One foot can't bear the weight anymore)
We'll each use one leg to walk.
Let's go.
(Disabled but resilient twins)
Let's keep walking.
Go.
Keep walking.
We don't know when we'll get out
of this desert.
Lizard.
Snake.
Rattlesnake.
The Farmer and the Snake.
(Actions 1: Suck out poisoned blood 2: Face-to-face energy healing
Lines 1: I'm in so much pain 2: Qi deviation)
Biting.
Bite marks.
Teeth.
It's an action.
It's...
Do you need me to suck out the poison?
(Got it in one second)
You're amazing.
This has his saliva on it.
I'll do it.
Use a straw. No need for this.
(Action 1: Suck out poisoned blood)
My brother,
I'm feeling refreshed now.
So smart.
(I'm in bad shape)
Again?
My arm is covered in saliva.
Hitting the wound. Action.
Hitting.
Me.
It hurts.
I'm in pain.
Reform thoroughly.
Pain.
He's in pain twice.
Yes.
Pain.
It hurts.
Got it.
It really hurts.
(Speak for me)
Really hurts.
It hurts.
I'm in pain.
You can lament.
I'm in pain!
I'm in so much pain.
(Line 1: I'm in so much pain)
I'm in so much pain!
It hurts more after being sucked.
You care about me, right?
Yes.
It's okay. For you,
I'd give my life for you.
Mom was right.
What?
You're kinder
and taller than me.
Calabash.
Hello.
Did someone bite you?
Or was your brother bitten?
My brother.
Your brother.
You're no longer a human.
I transform.
I put on airs.
I...
(Line 2: Qi deviation)
I'm harmless.
I...
I'm human...
No.
Demon.
I'm a demon.
I'm deviating.
(Line 2: Qi deviation)
What else?
Come on.
Well, I'm already deviating.
It's me who's deviating.
It's me.
It's you.
Let's go fight.
(Action 2: Face-to-face energy healing)
(Instant understanding)
Let's force out
the inner demons together.
(Action 2: Face-to-face energy healing)
Is it over?
Success.
This makes no sense.
It's over.
Over.
(That fast?)
He didn't even...
I haven't acted enough.
Not enough.
Four times.
(Wang Yuwen's team had 4 hints)
Good.
I didn't even do anything.
When I came up,
they were already healing each other.
I...
We just succeeded like that.
It's that simple.
Look at him.
So dedicated.
That's the commitment of a good actor.
Really biting.
Real feeling.
We're all about real listening,
real seeing, real feeling.
Really biting.
(Real taste)
It's really salty. Truly.
Come on, you two guess.
(Lin Yi and He perform, Jun and Xingxu guide)
Okay.
(Guides check the question)
How to give hints for this?
(Actions 1. Cockfight 2. Cover each other's mouths)
What's their big move?
(Lines 1. Guo Jing and Huang Rong 2. What is love in this world?)
Look at the answer.
(Checking the answer in advance)
This is very hard.
This one for you...
This is really very hard.
But can they think of it?
He can.
(Just watch)
Come on.
We can start now.
(Preset scenario: Fellow disciples dueling
out of jealousy over a junior sister)
Wait, you still don't understand
that we are lovers already?
You two are lovers?
You think
the one she likes is you?
Is it you then?
Last night,
she washed my socks.
You didn't know that, did you?
Are you that close?
Wait.
Or do my socks
(Still adding)
have a unique fragrance?
Wait a moment.
(Just shut up)
(Got anxious)
Before washing your socks,
she washed my dishes.
(Showing off)
Do you know why she washed your dishes?
Why?
She wanted to tell you
it's over
between you two.
Washing dishes for you.
Washing my socks means I'm very...
(Amazed by his own talent)
(Nothing to say to respond)
What a lame joke.
Even in ancient times,
you're using puns?
Losing to me, you don't need
to feel inferior.
Stop playing these
useless word games.
Draw your sword.
Come on.
(What does it mean?)
(Broadening the horizon)
I know you had hotpot yesterday.
(Creative)
So you're feeling a bit unwell today.
No need for medicine.
Being cut feels quite good.
Really?
You're addicted to this.
Come here.
My junior.
If you two keep this up,
waiting for junior sister won't help.
(Does anyone remember the mission?)
Right.
(Mission incoming)
Report, you two.
(Line 2: What is love in this world?)
Junior sister asked me to bring you two a message.
Yesterday, you two
both said the same romantic line to her.
But she forgot the first part.
The second part was
"it makes people willing
to die for love."
It makes people
willing to die for love.
Willing to die for love.
It makes people willing to die for love.
Two...
Two uneducated people.
Nice.
My junior.
(Mutual punishment
with one sword strike)
Stop just training martial arts.
Read some books.
I know.
My senior,
(Smart brain takes the lead)
what is love in this world?
(Line 2: What is love in this world?)
You two.
What do you say?
(Action 2: Cover each other's mouths)
You've learned
an earth-shattering secret of our sect.
Now the action you need to do is...
Tell everyone.
(Human loudspeaker)
No.
We can't let outsiders know.
So you need to...
One action.
(Hurry up)
(Crazy BBQ)
Don't let...
(Out of tricks)
Don't listen, it's a bad review.
Really?
(Cover the mouth)
Not this?
Not this.
Don't look, it's a bad review.
Alas.
Go.
Don't move.
How about doing it together?
- Hey.
- Together?
A bit lower.
Shut up.
(Action 2: Cover each other's mouths)
Well...
What?
(Line 1: Guo Jing and Huang Rong)
Our master taught us...
He taught us
a very powerful palm technique.
It can...
If you're hungry, go eat.
It's a kind of breakfast.
If you're hungry, go have breakfast.
A kind of breakfast.
Century egg and lean pork congee.
It's a kind of breakfast.
It's a kind of...
Breakfast.
Palm technique.
It has many numbers.
Eighteen Dragon Subduing Palms.
Who is this?
It's your...
Hong...
It's Guo Jing.
My senior, it's two people.
They're a couple.
A palm-fighting couple.
A couple with powerful palm techniques.
Guo Jing, Huang Rong.
(Line 1: Guo Jing and Huang Rong)
Good.
You two,
now you'll have the ultimate duel.
(Action 1: Cockfight)
The prop to use is...
Fei's feature today.
American quiff.
(Personally caught by me)
No.
(My junior, I can't keep up)
Use the American quiff
to stab the other to death.
Wait a second.
Calm down first.
Observe him.
What's he missing today?
Missing...
Missing a leg.
Right.
Let's have a duel!
Isn't this right?
(Action 1: Cockfight)
Junior sister is mine.
Not bad.
Wonderful.
How many hints did they use?
Over 100.
Seven hints.
Why seven?
Quite a lot, actually.
Really?
Let's congratulate the right side.
It's us?
(So surprised)
Really?
Oh, my.
Impossible.
How could it be us?
It's so difficult to defeat them.
It's us?
They're so strong, yet we...
(Unexpected)
They're so impressive.
Defeating them was really tough.
Let's invite the senior brother
of Qingcheng Sect
to infuse the winners with true energy.
Okay.
Who won?
We did.
We won.
Come on, get ready.
Okay.
Take my punch!
This is real kung fu.
Alright.
Okay.
Thank you, Sir.
Your prize really moves me.
You've put so much thought into it.
You don't need to rush.
You'll also have a chance
to get dark circles.
No.
No, take it slow.
Haste makes waste.
Training takes years.
We've given him true energy.
If you haven't trained, you haven't.
Do it like this.
Stick it on the belly button.
Whose belly button is crooked?
Really?
I just have one eye.
- Sorry.
- No need.
I'm telling you,
this looks most like a panda.
Trust me.
This is pretty good.
Okay.
Right.
It's gone.
Looks good.
Let's go eat.
Go.
We had so much fun.
Let's go.
Go.
So cool.
The usual spot.
Oh, my.
This camera is so close.
Already...
A bit closer and it'll be in my mouth.
Why not film like this?
We're already used to it.
Really?
I'm telling you,
when filmed,
it's exactly as you imagine.
A donkey face.
We're here, on the right.
Everyone says Chengdu food is delicious.
Exactly.
(Crispy Rice Pork Slices)
(Twice-cooked pork)
This looks delicious.
(Cold Spicy Beef)
(Fragrant bowl)
This is tasty.
I loved eating this as a kid.
What's that?
This is cold pot rabbit.
(Smashed cucumber)
Smashed cucumber.
Awesome!
Let's eat.
Come on.
This evening, we're eating
authentic Sichuan cuisine.
This is tasty.
Tasty.
Really?
Tasty rice.
This rice is so tasty.
Eat up quickly.
Here.
Want some?
Chicken foot tendons.
Okay, just a little.
Okay.
These chicken foot tendons are so tasty.
Tasty.
Really good.
So tasty.
Help!
Really tasty.
This is really good.
This is very delicious.
Really nice.
We can only make some sounds.
(Shockingly tasty)
(Pepper hitting incident)
So delicious.
Nice.
Every dish is tasty.
Today, I'm done for.
This morning, I swore a solemn oath
that I absolutely won't eat
spicy food again.
And then?
So delicious.
(Enjoying the food)
(Corn cake)
Is that cake sweet?
It's definitely not sweet.
I'll get you one.
(No)
I don't want it.
I don't.
I'll have one, thanks.
(Looking for the one who can share)
Let's share one.
I don't have enough.
You've eaten this, right?
Let's split.
It's very small.
Just one bite.
(Isn't this a piece of cake?)
Come on, eat it.
I want to have rice first.
(Planned)
This is my dessert.
I'm already on my second bowl.
She finished...
She finished two bowls.
Yeah, and I barely talk.
(Yuwen's immersive eating broadcast)
Delicious.
Is anyone in charge?
The kidney flowers are all gone.
(Lei feels wronged)
(Yuning feels wronged too)
I only had one piece.
(Report)
It's all in Wang Yuwen's plate.
Wang Yuwen took it.
(Merciless judge)
Did you take this?
I combined four dishes into one plate.
Got shot, huh? So wronged.
Nai,
give these last two
kidney flowers to him.
Kidney flowers, here.
Got it.
A very neat meal.
Finished two bowls of rice.
Now here comes a cake.
(Neat eater)
She absolutely won't share.
Come on, everyone.
To our lovely Sichuan.
Cheers.
Traveling the martial world,
no matter how amazing
your martial arts skills,
you must get the secret code right.
Meeting, passing messages,
code matching.
This is a required course
in the martial world.
If the code matches, you're one of us.
If not, you might be exposed
or even lose your life.
Today, you'll complete
a martial world challenge
about secret codes.
It's called
Smile Often.
Act on my signal.
Since you're already so in sync,
we have to make it harder.
Who's dawdling?
In sync.
Okay.
Just ten centimeters off,
and you can't hear clearly?
I really couldn't hear.
(Teams of three, one guesses, two pass the word.)
Nine people split into three groups for the charades challenge.
In each round,
one person wears headphones and guesses.
Two wear mouth openers and cooperate.
They shout to pass the words.
The passers can only use
lip movements and shouting
to convey the word.
Aside from hinting at tones,
they can't make any other actions.
They can do this.
Third tone, right?
Yes, tones.
It's completely meaningless.
If you can't even
make out the characters,
the tones...
(Sharp review)
Each round lasts eight minutes.
(Each round lasts eight minutes)
The team with the most correct answers wins.
So how...
How do we split?
I think we should go by age.
You think so?
Do you want to be in a group
with me and Honglei?
(Seriously)
Our senior group will destroy them.
(Watching the drama)
Okay?
What do you say?
Are you confident?
I'm the youngest here.
If you yell at me, I can't talk back.
If he yells at me,
I can't talk back either.
(We're the same)
Yeah.
But we dare not yell at him.
You can.
He can't hear you.
How about this?
Just right.
One, two, three.
This works too.
That works.
(Keep Smiling
Group 1, Group 2, Group 3)
Lin Yi, the three of us are a group.
Are you aware of the situation?
Yes.
Okay.
We're definitely winning, you know.
Why?
(Why so sure?)
I'm just talking big here.
(That's it?)
(Can't bear to look)
(What are you doing?)
What are you getting high on?
It's just very easy.
(Still talking big)
An easy game.
A piece of cake.
Let's have a round first.
Let's go.
(Confidently going into battle)
Come on.
You guess first.
(Li Naiwen and Lin Yi pass the word, Liu Yuning guesses)
I'll guess.
(Preparation)
I'm ready.
They think this is cute?
(Unbelievable)
Move back a bit.
I'm afraid I'll spit on your face.
(This distance is dangerous)
It's fine.
(Already prepared)
I've already put on my glasses.
Spitting on my face is okay.
Just don't spit in my eyes.
(I'll try my best)
Can you speak?
See if you can speak.
Yes.
Okay.
Can you see us clearly?
Your teeth are so straight.
Alright, let's go.
Ready.
Three, two, one, go.
(Bowling)
Four characters.
First character.
The first.
Hit.
Teeth?
(Cheerful)
Stupid.
(Forcefully)
Hit.
Teeth?
De.
Hit.
(You're adorably weird)
Ya?
Hit.
Pull.
(I'm exhausted, I'm silent)
(Be patient)
Hit.
(What does it mean?)
Fake?
You're even forming words now.
Hit.
(Savor it)
Big.
Right.
Blink?
It's over.
There's an idiot among them.
I feel like the three of them
will be at it until dawn.
Forget it.
The last three characters.
Third character.
Last three characters.
Watch my mouth.
(Liu Yuning's perspective)
Wow.
(Look closer)
Certain.
He moved closer.
(Can't hold it in anymore)
(Serious)
Watch.
(Liu Yuning's perspective)
Meh?
How can you guess this?
The fourth character.
Fourth character.
Ball.
(Was I like that?)
You didn't do anything.
From my perspective, you did nothing.
You were like this.
(Speaking up for myself)
That's it.
(Requesting a pause)
Come on, let's switch.
Someone else can sit here.
Let's see if you can guess.
(Really out of ideas)
I really can't guess.
(Impossible)
It's impossible to guess.
This is so hard.
(Kong Rong Gives Away the Pear)
Four characters.
First character.
Kong.
Old.
Roar.
Kong.
Do.
Fall.
Kong.
Lotus root.
(Kong, cracked voice version)
Kong.
(Already exhausted)
Grass.
All four characters together.
Together.
Kong Rong Gives Away the Pear.
(Li Naiwen's perspective)
(Full of hope)
Isn't this cursing?
He thinks they are
secretly cursing at him.
Third character.
Gives away.
Him.
Coffee.
Gives away.
Coffee, coffee.
(Breaking down)
This hard?
Fourth character.
Pear.
(Leaning in to look)
Like this.
Okay.
Tell me.
From your perspective,
are they just two mad dogs?
Yes.
I'm really...
(Helpless)
Lin Yi, try to guess.
(Send the abstract god)
Come down and rest first.
We have to score at least one.
This game is impossible.
Okay.
(Tyrannosaurus Rex)
Three characters.
(Serious thinking)
Ba.
Mom.
Scold.
Wrong.
Ba.
Second character. Wang.
Wang.
(Clueless)
(Using force too)
Mom, parents.
No.
Wang.
Okay.
Why are you laughing?
Third.
Long.
(Silent, just blindly imitating)
Grandma.
Long.
(Movements also in sync)
Tyranosaurus Rex.
(Correct answer)
(Impressive)
(Showcasing a little skill)
Ba.
(Little brain replaying)
Ba. Wang.
Lin Yi is very smart.
He's looking for patterns.
He's still pondering.
He's reviewing.
(Fully affirmative)
This kid.
Yes.
(Recognition from the opponent)
Four characters.
(Western Cowboy)
West.
Chicken.
Seven.
West.
Second character.
Department.
Female.
Scold.
Department.
Afraid.
Dad.
Department.
Bad.
(Serves as a conductor)
Department.
Thrilling.
Spicy.
Department.
Hang.
Awkward.
Department.
There.
Bah! Tah! Chah!
Chah! Hah! Lah! Chah!
(Making up for the lack of rain in Chengdu)
First character.
(Don't panic)
West!
(Xi'an?)
Xi'an!
West!
Department.
Xi mu?
No!
West!
Road.
Department.
Western!
Western Cowboy!
So amazing.
(Margherita Pizza)
(Silence is deafening)
(Waiting quietly for a good show)
This is way too hard.
It's hard to make the connection.
Six characters.
First character.
Are you kissing?
Mar.
Right now. Ma!
Second character.
Gher.
Bigger.
Mar.
Gher.
(Really hard to hold back)
Third character.
La.
(Read my lips)
Ri.
Lai?
Lai.
(Assisted pronunciation)
Ri.
Mary!
This was the third character.
Mar-what-ri?
There's a fourth character.
Ta.
Ke!
(Perked up again)
Ri!
Margherita.
Alright.
Pizza.
Five and six.
(Rain proof preparation)
(Manual protection)
(Preemptive defense)
(Seriously on guard)
(Always ready)
It's fine.
Something was in my eye.
(Protected)
It's fine. Hurry, say it!
It got into his eye.
Pizza.
Mi.
Sixth character.
Zi?
Xi. Si.
Za!
Margherita-what-za?
Watch me.
Za.
Read my lips.
Pi.
Mi.
Moo.
No.
Pi.
Poo.
Boo.
Margherita.
Poo-za.
(Does that sound right?)
Pizza.
(Brain is fried)
What? What's the word?
Poo.
Just poo it.
Pi.
Pizza!
Margherita Pizza!
That's amazing!
You're incredible!
You even know Margherita Pizza!
This is too hard!
Well done.
Okay.
That's enough.
(Li Naiwen's team
answered three questions correctly)
Found your weakness.
Seriously.
I've never been this bad at a game.
This one's really hard.
Come on, you three.
Let's go.
So, who's guessing?
I'll guess.
Let He go first.
(Everything is ready)
You guys are pretty cute.
What's so hard about this?
(Confidence is rising)
It's not hard at all.
Stay calm.
Right.
(Barrier-free communication in progress)
Okay, come on. Ready?
Three, two, one, go!
(Nunchaku)
Double.
(Switching to Lei)
Hot.
Chen He doesn't take a loss at all.
It's like he's biting back.
(This kid is hopeless)
(Taking turns in relay)
What?
(Enjoying)
Double.
(Completely predicted)
In his perspective, that's what it is.
(That was so expected)
What are you wowing about?
Double.
Chua.
Come on!
Whatever.
(The princess gives up)
I can't guess it.
Switch!
He's totally lost.
(Too hilarious)
How many characters?
(Ready to go)
(Kung Fu Panda)
Four characters.
First character.
Ha!
Roar.
(Determined)
(Full-barrier communication)
(Go)
(Forcing the princess to take the stage)
Gong.
O.
Roar.
Gong.
You.
Go.
Gong.
Charge.
Gong!
You.
You!
No, first character first.
First character first.
(I'll leave first)
(Focused on the game)
Say it.
(Calm down)
Four characters.
First character.
Second character.
Third character.
Fourth character.
Kung Fu Panda.
(Playing so dirty)
What? Did it fall out?
So much effort!
Give up? Switch!
What is it?
Kung Fu Panda!
This is way too hard!
(Looks hard, actually not simple at all)
This is tricky.
Tricky.
Come on!
I'll try.
Try it.
Even when wearing braces,
you can still hiccup?
(Factory settings included)
(Glamorous)
How many characters?
Four.
Four characters.
No rush.
(Seriously guessing)
Take your time.
No rush.
Light.
Say it again.
Read it like a poem.
(Poetic inspiration strikes)
Light.
Ba.
(Whose ancient-style boy is here?)
Which word is easiest to say?
I thought they were all pretty easy.
Guang, Xian, Liang!
The two monsters are strategizing.
What do you say?
Which word is easiest?
I think they're all pretty easy.
Fourth character.
Li.
You.
Fourth character, Li.
Third character.
Honglei, the third.
(Eyes on me)
Honglei, the third one.
Liang!
Liang.
(Eyebrows also exerting force)
Liang Li!
(Smart IQ occupying the high ground)
Bite off more than you can chew?
Act within your limits?
Xian.
What?
Don't get violent.
(Suggest using your mouth)
Second character.
(Calm down)
Second character again.
Second character.
Second. Two.
Liang, Li. Three and four.
Second character.
Xian.
Xian, Liang, Li.
Glamorous.
(It still has to be the old-timer)
You're incredible.
(The big brain)
He's exhausted, I think.
(Brain overloaded)
(Ear pick)
- Three.
- Three characters.
(This looks great)
Wa.
Ma.
Ba.
(Very close)
Wa.
(Not a still image)
Er.
You're just gaping in front of him.
(Experience of a veteran)
Come on. "Er"...
"Er" is probably...
"Er" is a dead end.
Third character.
Shao.
(All the same mouth shape)
Qiang?
Shao.
Zhang.
Useless...
Useless too.
(No one works)
What is it?
Useless too.
Even the character "wa" came out.
The sounds you're making now
sound like an old man.
I've shouted myself hoarse.
(Life's matte moment)
(Lost all strength and means)
Say it again.
Shao.
Shang.
Which character?
Well said, "shang".
[*"Shang" means "reward"]
Wa-what-shang?
Wa-what-shao.
Wa-what?
Shao.
Wa-what-shao.
Wa-what-shao?
(Panic turned off the brain)
Wa-what-shao.
Honglei.
Ear pick.
Ear pick, right?
Yes.
(Sun Honglei's team got two right)
Experience counts.
Nice.
So hard.
Honestly, way too hard.
(Tired from laughing)
Which one of us guesses?
I'll guess.
You guess.
You both have nicer teeth than me.
My teeth are the ugliest.
(Pretty little fangs)
Let's see who comes in last.
(Aiming for last place)
We'll fight for it.
Fight for last place.
Right.
Fight for it.
(Round 3 begins)
It feels like
you're completely defenseless,
like your hands and feet are tied.
(Helpless)
(Naples)
Four...
Four characters.
Na.
Da.
Second.
Bu.
(Watching seriously)
Po.
Bo.
He can close his mouth.
(Working out both the body
and the mouth)
Na Bu.
Right.
That's impossible.
[*"Na Bu Ke Neng" in Chinese]
(Indeed impossible)
Le.
Na Bu De.
The fourth one.
Naples?
That's impressive.
(How can they guess so fast?)
Quite smug.
(GG Bond)
This one's easy.
Three?
Okay, first character.
First character.
Zhu.
(Watch my mouth)
Bu?
Zhu.
Bu.
(Who can tell if it's "zhu" or "bu"?)
You pig.
Tu?
Zhu.
Du?
Tu?
Zhu.
Zhu Zhu.
Second character. Zhu Zhu.
Third one.
Xia.
Zhu Zhu Cha?
(Now with the move)
Zhu Zhu Up.
Zhu Zhu, up.
Xia.
GG Bond?
Switch.
Okay, time out.
Time out.
Who's up? You do it?
I'll guess.
You guess.
Four characters.
(Sliced beef offal in chili sauce)
Fu.
First character.
(The hardest episode
to hold back laughter)
What?
(What does that mean?)
Look at me.
Fu.
Si?
Mua?
Fu.
He's crying.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
I can guess it.
Don't cry.
My tears are coming out.
(The laughs keep piling up)
Second character.
Qi.
Ji?
Xi?
Qi.
Ji, Qi, Xi?
Qi, second.
Ji.
Qi.
Third.
Fei.
Mei.
Lei.
Fei.
Qi Fei.
Sliced beef offal in chili sauce.
(Awesome)
Nice.
Come on.
(Love Till Death)
Five characters.
First.
Si.
Si?
Die with grievance?
Si Ye...
Love Till Death.
Amazing.
(What a clever glamorous queen)
No need to guess the rest.
(Aladdin's Lamp)
Five characters.
First character.
A.
Second character.
La.
Alaska?
Third character.
Aladdin.
Ding.
(Believe in yourself and fill it in)
Aladdin's
Lamp.
(Heartbroken)
Four characters.
First one.
Xin.
(Decoded instantly)
(Anticipating)
Sir,
your dentures fell out.
Your dentures fell out.
Fei, doesn't it fit or something?
It's the mouth.
I have a small mouth, okay?
(58cm head, tiny mouth)
I'm dying laughing.
Second character.
(Still trying)
Heartbroken.
Very impressive.
Hurry.
(Balala the Fairies)
Six.
How many characters?
Six characters.
This should be pretty hard too.
(Balala the Fairies)
Amazing.
Balala the Fairies.
Time's up.
(Guo Jingfei's team got seven right)
Totally convinced.
(Opponent is subdued)
Impressive.
You're made for dentistry.
(Truly admirable)
Well,
he's the highlight of this game.
His mouth is tight.
Xingxu opens his mouth
in a very standard way.
Yes.
In Wow The World S2,
since most games are guessing games,
having Yuwen
means having the world.
(Certified by Fei
as the guessing master)
If the team
also had Lin Yi,
they'd basically be invincible.
They just need to get his point.
We have the instruction manual.
(Mastering the manual means invincible)
Instruction manual.
The winners' reward this time
is still panda eyes.
Do we have to punch them out?
(Purely handmade)
(Already prepared)
(Also prepared)
About the reward for the three of them,
do you want to help them achieve it?
What?
Draw panda eyes.
(Eager to try)
Honglei,
pick someone you like.
I like Jingfei, of course.
(I knew it)
Who likes Yuwen?
We all like Yuwen.
Let's each draw one stroke then.
Yeah, I think everyone
should each draw one stroke.
And I'll draw on Jingfei alone.
Give it a try.
Feel it.
(Can't hold it in)
Why does the panda have eyebrows?
New style panda.
(All artistic creations)
I'll draw one
on Fei too.
I'll draw one on myself later.
Let me draw one for you here.
This is cute.
This is drawn really well.
Who else wants a little panda?
Do you want one?
I'll draw one for you.
Go ahead.
Draw it here for him.
This is pretty cute.
Not bad, Jun.
The one on your face is pretty cute.
She drew it for you.
Jun, draw this head for him.
Okay.
Draw that head on Fei's face.
Well,
this is a reward for winning the game?
I really don't get it.
(Punishment or reward? My call)
Right?
I don't get it.
It's like a punishment.
Okay, little panda.
Okay.
Draw one for me.
- Let's stick and draw.
- Okay.
I'll just blacken the tip of your nose.
Then we stick them on.
Okay.
Alright?
We're so funny.
It looks pretty good like this.
It's actually okay.
Not bad.
Pretty good.
Really good-looking.
Really not bad.
It has an overall design.
Very good-looking.
Everyone needs a beard?
No.
We three don't look like winners.
If we stand outside,
everyone will think
we're being punished.
(Reputation-wise)
Yeah, we three don't look like winners.
Come on, present our
Qingcheng Sect treasure.
This time it's real.
This is
the real deal?
A little figure pops out.
I see it and I'm stressed.
Qingcheng Sect's supreme
eight-character enlightenment motto.
Eat well, sleep well.
We three have been tired all day
and ended up like this.
And they're telling us
to eat well and sleep well?
Congratulations.
Awesome.
Congratulations on completing today's
Kung Fu Meow tour.
The world is big,
but three meals a day is bigger.
No matter how far you travel,
in the end, it's all for peace of mind,
to eat every meal well,
and to sleep well every night.
So here we wish everyone
good night.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
Good work.
Without today,
we can still sleep well.
(Through life's storms,
with true friends, joy is everywhere)
(Next Episode Preview)
First mission:
Cooling Challenge.
Let us old folks be in a team.
Don't include me, okay?
It's a song title?
You should pretend
you can sing everything.
♪The cicadas are♪
What's that? What's wrong?
Like someone touched my head.
Your head's already drenched flat.
Stop it.
Whoever I touch sings.
The heavens spare no one.
It's like the sea rushed towards me.
I just felt like
it was like a tsunami.
Wow, the world is really fresh.
Is this some kind of revenge drama?
This is Wow The World's
own water-splashing festival.
(Stay tuned for Earth Group's
Cooling Challenge)
Split into two teams
and start cooking.
We have Yuwen.
We're not afraid of Liu Yuning now.
Come on, let's cook.
Let me show off a bit.
There's something.
(What exactly is their mission?)
You Know What I Mean,
multiplayer version.
What is this?
Chinese opera?
Bulldozer? Shaving the hair?
Heart attack.
Yes.
Don't be nervous.
Why are you acting like you won?
There's a twist.
(Who will ultimately win?)
Taboo Word Restaurant.
No words with "wo", "ni", or "ta".
[*Personal pronouns in Chinese]
I'll say "this humble one".
"This humble person".
"This one".
His logic is correct.
Let's cheer first, okay?
Absolutely.
We absolutely won't say
"wo", "ni", or "ta".
Let's go.
Handsome guys first.
Then "mu men" shall take the first step.
[*Internet slang for "we"]
"Wu deng" are hungry.
[*Classical Chinese for "we"]
Be extremely careful.
The hands are sweating.
Hold on.
(Will Earth Group get to eat?)
You will complete the performance
of the new theme song.
Good evening.
A theme song for this season.
No one has heard it before.
That's right.
You're the first to hear it.
Thank you all.
(Stay tuned for the Earth Group's
brilliant performance)
(Extra Episode Preview)
We'll play a game about teamwork.
For example, within these ten seconds,
we get in the car.
But there's a photographer in the car.
We'll be photographed too.
Then we'll have to
take out the photographer.
And grab his phone.
Look how much Honglei
resembles a fighting dog.
(Fight)
The idea of grabbing excites him.
(Too tall to be an advantage)
Taller people are harder to hide, right?
(Tall trio)
You guys are at a disadvantage.
I'll tell you the coolest way to play.
Come on, the Bonjour team.
"Stupid Pig" team.
[*Bonjour and Stupid Pig sound alike]
Let's go.
Slow down.
Naiwen.
Let's go.
Get in.
Okay.
You guys...
Black-clad big guys.
Get in quickly.
Hurry.
Which car is next?
Diagonally opposite.
Get down.
(Can the Earth Group
complete the challenge?)
(Extra Episode Preview)
Everyone needs to pick
the best gift for the person they drew.
This looks a lot like Chaoyue.
A parrot toilet.
That one-of-a-kind piece is really nice.
Okay.
Is this handmade?
And there's only one, right?
I think this looks like you.
I think the pattern
is beautifully drawn.
This looks exactly like my clown
from the other day.
This is Yang Chaoyue.
(What kind of gifts
will the Earth Group give?)
(Wow The World, show schedule)